9:35/O AM/O Windows/O 8/O has/O taken/O its/O share/O of/O lumps/O over/O the/O past/O few/O months/O ,/O but/O one/O analyst/O thinks/O its/O troubles/O all/O began/O with/O Microsoftâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY s/O MSFT/O decision/O to/O omit/O the/O Start/O button/O from/O its/O user/O interface/O ./O 
In/O an/O interview/O with/O CNET/ORGANIZATION ,/O IDC/ORGANIZATION analyst/O Bob/PERSON Oâ/PERSON $/MONEY ™/MONEY Donnell/ORGANIZATION says/O that/O not/O having/O a/O Start/O button/O is/O a/O big/O turnoff/O to/O many/O users/O who/O have/O spent/O years/O working/O with/O Windows/O and/O who/O have/O come/O to/O expect/O it/O as/O a/O central/O feature/O of/O any/O Windows/O device/O ./O 
â/O $/MONEY œThere/MONEY were/O certain/O decisions/O that/O Microsoft/ORGANIZATION made/O that/O were/O in/O retrospect/O flawed/O ,/O â/O $/MONEY says/MONEY Oâ/MONEY $/MONEY ™/MONEY Donnell/ORGANIZATION ./O 
â/O $/MONEY œNotably/MONEY not/O allowing/O people/O to/O boot/O into/O desktop/O mode/O and/O taking/O away/O the/O start/O button/O ./O 
Those/O two/O things/O have/O come/O up/O consistently/O ./O 
Weâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY ve/O done/O some/O research/O and/O people/O miss/O that/O ./O 
â/O $/O Not/O booting/O up/O in/O desktop/O mode/O is/O seen/O as/O particularly/O pointless/O ,/O Oâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY Donnell/O explains/O ,/O because/O most/O users/O do/O all/O their/O work/O in/O desktop/O mode/O on/O their/O PCs/O and/O rarely/O use/O the/O tiled/O interface/O unless/O theyâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY re/O on/O a/O tablet/O ./O 
Oâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY Donnell/ORGANIZATION says/O that/O several/O OEMs/O have/O apparently/O been/O imploring/O Microsoft/ORGANIZATION to/O bring/O back/O the/O Start/O button/O and/O add/O an/O option/O to/O boot/O up/O in/O desktop/O mode/O ,/O but/O adds/O that/O he/O wouldnâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY t/O be/O surprised/O if/O Microsoft/ORGANIZATION stuck/O to/O its/O guns/O and/O didnâ/O $/MONEY ™/MONEY t/O significantly/O alter/O its/O approach/O ./O 
